

# Gökalp Giray

# Frontend Developer

**★** gokalpgiray.github.io/Portfolio/ **in** gokalpgiray **(**) GokalpGiray

### **₽** Profile

Hello. I wanted to embody my interest in software development, which has started in the last years of my university life, and turn it into my profession. I have chosen frontend development as a new career path for myself. For this purpose, I am still working hard. Using the work ethic and discipline I've gained from my work experience for many years, I am trying to become an expert in this field by constantly improving myself. You can check my work on my GitHub page.

### **Education**

2015 – 2020	Bachelor's Degree, Survey Engineering, Çanakkale Onsekiz Mart University ⊘	Çanakkale, Turkey
2014 – 2015	English Preparation, School of Foreign Languages, Karadeniz Technical University ⊘	Trabzon, Turkey
2010 – 2014	<b>High School, Math - Science,</b> Fahreddin Kerim Gökay Anatolian High School	İstanbul, Turkey

## Professional Experience

	•	
07/2021 - 09/2022	<b>Survey Engineer,</b> 3408/22 No'lu Lisanslı Harita Kadastro Mühendislik Bürosu	Istanbul, Turkey
02/2020 - 07/2021	<b>Quality Control Specialist,</b> <i>GKN Sinter İstanbul Metal San. ve Tic.A.Ş.</i>	Istanbul, Turkey
07/2019 - 01/2020	Travel Consultant, Capacity Jolly Tur	Istanbul, Turkey
12/2018 - 03/2019	<b>Intern Survey Engineer,</b> 1706/98 No'lu Lisanslı Harita Kadastro Mühendislik Bürosu	Çanakkale, Turkey
07/2017 – 09/2017	Intern Survey Engineer, Küçükçekmece Kadastro Birimi	Istanbul, Turkey

### Projects

**Gurme Şef 1974,** The website I prepared for Gurme Şef 1974 *∂* 

diyetisyenbuseakduman.com, The website I prepared for Expert Dietitian Buse Akduman ⊘

#### Disney+ Clone,

I cloned the Disney+ site as a demo. Don't forget to login to the site with your Google account;) ∂

**Contacts App,** I developed a simple contact app using React and Redux. *∂* 

**Breaking Bad App,** Using React and Redux, I developed a simple application that contains the characters and words of the Breaking Bad series.  $\varnothing$ 

### <u>@</u>

### Skills

- React
   JavaScript
- HTML

• CSS

- Bootstrap
- Redux

- Matlab
- git

Java

MS Office

# **&** Languages

සිං Familiar With

**English** (Intermediate)

Turkish (Native Language)

### **Agile**

Scrum and Kanban

### *ල*ී

#### **Interests**

#### **Basketball**

I have been watching, playing, listening and following basketball for many years. Even though I can't watch the matches all the time, I somehow follow the leagues.

#### Formula 1

Especially in recent years, my interest in Formula 1, which I watched as a child, has flared up again. I try to follow it as closely as possible. Forza Ferrari!

#### **Tennis**

I've been watching and playing since I was a kid. This sport taught me to manage my ambition and patience.

### **战** References

<u>**Oğuz Özkeroğlu**</u>, *Lead Developer*, Ericsson Sweden oguz.ozkeroglu@ericsson.com, +46 72 300 50 80

<u>Serhat Akkuş</u>, *Software Lead* serhatakkus@gmail.com, +90 535 610 64 33

<u>Melek Pazarbaşı</u>, *Software Engineer*, ING Türkiye melekp30@gmail.com, +90 538 979 22 90

<u>Taha Furkan Tarakçı</u>, Frontend Developer tahatarakci34@gmail.com, +90 535 255 61 47

### ဂ္ဂါ

### **Certificates**

HTML5 and CSS3 Fundamentals ⊘